Woke up quick at about noon. Just
Woke up quick at about noon. Just thought that I had to be in Compton soon. I
thought that I had to be in Compton soon. I
thought that I had be in Compton soon. I got to get drunk before the day begins
ran in the house. He grabbed a clip with
ran in the house. He grabbed a clip with the back 10 on the side of my hip.
the back 10 on the side of my hip.
the back 10 on the side of my hip. Failed outside my weapon just about the
Failed outside my weapon just about the
Failed outside my weapon just about the fles jumping the boy juice inside my
fles jumping the boy juice inside my
fles jumping the boy juice inside my play ship. Miami away was gangster
play ship. Miami away was gangster
play ship. Miami away was gangster gangster to the top of the list and I
gangster to the top of the list and I
gangster to the top of the list and I play my own sh with someone like this
play my own sh with someone like this
play my own sh with someone like this who's down the street in my six jacking
who's down the street in my six jacking
who's down the street in my six jacking the  slapping the ho went to the
the  slapping the ho went to the
the  slapping the ho went to the park getting
park getting
park getting Knuckle hands out the cold. Shoot some
Knuckle hands out the cold. Shoot some
Knuckle hands out the cold. Shoot some moves. Stop pull up the canopy. A fresh
moves. Stop pull up the canopy. A fresh
moves. Stop pull up the canopy. A fresh up from your roll with start
up from your roll with start
up from your roll with start making that GTA
making that GTA
making that GTA cuz the boys in the
cuz the boys in the
cuz the boys in the heart
cuz I ain't  Born as hell. I don't
cuz I ain't  Born as hell. I don't want to get ill. So I went to SP my home
want to get ill. So I went to SP my home
want to get ill. So I went to SP my home boys chill the fell that's out there
boys chill the fell that's out there
boys chill the fell that's out there making that up with the monster how big
making that up with the monster how big
making that up with the monster how big 40 and I stop
40 and I stop
40 and I stop left my m I hit the back out said that
left my m I hit the back out said that
left my m I hit the back out said that she said something I couldn't believe so
she said something I couldn't believe so
she said something I couldn't believe so I grabbed the stupid  as we she
I grabbed the stupid  as we she
I grabbed the stupid  as we she thought  would not back up slap the
thought  would not back up slap the
thought  would not back up slap the ho jump up and she's supposed to shout
ho jump up and she's supposed to shout
ho jump up and she's supposed to shout so right crossing knocked his knock his
so right crossing knocked his knock his
so right crossing knocked his knock his own ass out the boys in
trash for your
trash for your no but to be legit don't pull me forward
no but to be legit don't pull me forward
no but to be legit don't pull me forward cuz I hate said  blowing hard now
cuz I hate said  blowing hard now
cuz I hate said  blowing hard now under control then wrapped the s around
under control then wrapped the s around
under control then wrapped the s around a telephone pole I looked at my to I
a telephone pole I looked at my to I
a telephone pole I looked at my to I said oh brother I f in the gutter and go
said oh brother I f in the gutter and go
said oh brother I f in the gutter and go find a walking home and I see a d ride
find a walking home and I see a d ride
find a walking home and I see a d ride no cat is driving on the side big bust
no cat is driving on the side big bust
no cat is driving on the side big bust to got pulled over copy no Happy
to got pulled over copy no Happy
to got pulled over copy no Happy visiting the rest
visiting the rest
visiting the rest now. GL
now. GL
now. GL sometimes.
So now your
So now your knowing nothing in life but to be the
knowing nothing in life but to be the
knowing nothing in life but to be the boy cuz I ain't said  Yeah. Yeah.